{
    "id": "e5a17bd6f227407487577f382d7c3c59",
    "title": "I Wish, I’d Rather, And Had Better",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7fdcee6ee4734e0ebf8960f3b8b91a6e",
            "title": "I Wish, I'd Rather, I'd Better",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I would rather you ........................... at me.",
                    "description": "After would rather, we use a past tense with a present meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't shout",
                        "didn't shout"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ........................ work on Saturdays.",
                    "description": "After I wish, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't have to",
                        "didn't have to",
                        "hadn't to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You'd better ....................... me my money back.",
                    "description": "After had better, we use the infinitive without to (first form of the verb).",
                    "answers": [
                        "give",
                        "gave",
                        "given"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "After the way he behaved at my party, I wish I ......................... him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't invite",
                        "don't invite",
                        "hadn't invited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I'd rather ........................... up early on Sundays.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not get",
                        "don't get",
                        "didn't get"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The program starts at 6 o'clock. You had better ..................... late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not be",
                        "not to be",
                        "be not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I'd rather you ........................... on Tuesday than Monday.",
                    "description": "After would rather, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "come",
                        "came",
                        "had come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ............................. to work tomorrow.",
                    "description": "After I wish, we use a past tense with present meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't have",
                        "didn't have",
                        "won't have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you …………………. insist on leaving early.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "won't",
                        "wouldn't",
                        "hadn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You'd better ........................... him with your crude jokes.",
                    "description": "After had better, we use an infinitive without to. Negative forms are made by putting not before the infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "not offend",
                        "to not offend",
                        "not to offend"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ........................... get a scholarship.",
                    "description": "A past tense is used with present meaning after would rather. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you .............................. leave me alone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}